# SHAWN MCCLAIN IMPLEMENTATION PROJECT MANAGER

#### **Summary**

I am a junior data scientist and technical project manager with a versatile set of skills. From my education and personal projects, I have technical experience data wrangling with the Pandas and Numpy packages in Python, visualizing data with Matplotlib and Seaborn, and applying Machine Learning techniques through the Keras, StatsModels, and Scikit-Learn packages. From my professional background, I have experience leading and organizing data conversion projects with high scale clients.

#### **Employment**

Vertafore Denver Implementation Project Manager Jan. 2020 to Current

- -Assisting and guiding customers through the conversion process to convert their source data to a Vertafore system.
- -Executing projects and service agreements for new and existing clients.
- -Coordinating and organizing the efforts of teammates on projects.
- -Making sure implementation processes are on schedule and are to the client's liking.

## Jeju Special Governing Province Seogwipo English Teacher Jan. 2018 to Feb. 2019

- Delivered English lessons to Elementary and Middle school students.
- Managed classroom logistics and disciplinary actions when necessary
- Created interactive learning games using PowerPoint and Word.
- Conducted and orchestrated English camps during the Summer and Winter breaks.
- Created and prepared examination materials for language proficiency

#### **Projects**

#### **Contact**

sh9wntm@gmail.com

github.com/Shawn-tm

**~** 7206217609

#### **Education**

Springboard Data Science Career Track

Dec. 2019 to Current

University of Colorado Boulder

Aug. 2012 to Spring 2017

**BA Economics 2017** 

#### Skills

#### **DATA SCIENCE**

Numpy

Python

Keras Github

Sci-kit Learn

**Machine Learning** 

**Pandas** 

SQL

**StatsModels** 

**Convolutional Neural Nets** 

Style Transfer

**Unsupervised Learning** 

### TECHNICAL PROJECT MANAGEMENT

Teaching
Public Speaking
Time Management
Database Provisioning
Team Facilitation
Change Management